export const questions = [{"id": 1, "question": "Which of the following is an internal source of finance for a sole trader?", "options": ["A: Option 1", "B: Option 2", "C: Option 3", "D: Option 4"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 2, "question": "Which of the following would be classified as a corporate social responsibility activity?", "options": ["A: Option 5", "B: Option 6", "C: Option 7", "D: Option 8"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 3, "question": "Which of the following functional areas would be responsible for managing the expectations of guests in a large hotel?", "options": ["A: Option 9", "B: Option 10", "C: Option 11", "D: Option 12"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 4, "question": "What is the correct term for an organisation where all important decisions are made at the head office?", "options": ["A: Option 13", "B: Option 14", "C: Option 15", "D: Option 16"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 5, "question": "Ignoring which of the following stakeholders is most likely to lead to a company being denied planning permission?", "options": ["A: Option 17", "B: Option 18", "C: Option 19", "D: Option 20"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 6, "question": "Which of the following would not be included in the "resource requirements" section of a business plan?", "options": ["A: Option 21", "B: Option 22", "C: Option 23", "D: Option 24"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 7, "question": "According to the cash flow statement, which of the following statements is true?", "options": ["A: Option 25", "B: Option 26", "C: Option 27", "D: Option 28"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 8, "question": "The company appears to have broken the:", "options": ["A: Option 29", "B: Option 30", "C: Option 31", "D: Option 32"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 9, "question": "Which of the following is an example of an inventor?", "options": ["A: Option 33", "B: Option 34", "C: Option 35", "D: Option 36"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 10, "question": "As a supplier, one of Parsley plc"s main objectives is to:", "options": ["A: Option 37", "B: Option 38", "C: Option 39", "D: Option 40"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 11, "question": "Which two functional areas of the bakery are working together?", "options": ["A: Option 41", "B: Option 42", "C: Option 43", "D: Option 44"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 12, "question": "A supervisor with a wide span of control:", "options": ["A: Option 45", "B: Option 46", "C: Option 47", "D: Option 48"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 13, "question": "The term "closing inventory" on a company"s income statement refers to:", "options": ["A: Option 49", "B: Option 50", "C: Option 51", "D: Option 52"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 14, "question": "According to the estimates, Jamal Botterill"s break-even level of output for 2023 will be:", "options": ["A: Option 53", "B: Option 54", "C: Option 55", "D: Option 56"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 15, "question": "What task is most likely to be part of the job role of the chief executive of a public limited company?", "options": ["A: Option 57", "B: Option 58", "C: Option 59", "D: Option 60"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 16, "question": ""A new prime minister leading the UK government" would be an example of:", "options": ["A: Option 61", "B: Option 62", "C: Option 63", "D: Option 64"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 17, "question": "Which of the following is a financial factor which may negatively affect a supermarket"s success?", "options": ["A: Option 65", "B: Option 66", "C: Option 67", "D: Option 68"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 18, "question": "According to the pie chart:", "options": ["A: Option 69", "B: Option 70", "C: Option 71", "D: Option 72"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 19, "question": "An overdraft would be recorded in a statement of financial position as a:", "options": ["A: Option 73", "B: Option 74", "C: Option 75", "D: Option 76"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 20, "question": "Which of the following is a correct definition of the term "demographics"?", "options": ["A: Option 77", "B: Option 78", "C: Option 79", "D: Option 80"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 21, "question": "Which of the following is an internal source of finance for a sole trader?", "options": ["A: Option 81", "B: Option 82", "C: Option 83", "D: Option 84"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 22, "question": "Which of the following would be classified as a corporate social responsibility activity?", "options": ["A: Option 85", "B: Option 86", "C: Option 87", "D: Option 88"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 23, "question": "Which of the following is part of the job role of the chief executive of a public limited company?", "options": ["A: Option 89", "B: Option 90", "C: Option 91", "D: Option 92"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 24, "question": "Which of the following is a flat organisational structure?", "options": ["A: Option 93", "B: Option 94", "C: Option 95", "D: Option 96"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 25, "question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of being a sole trader?", "options": ["A: Option 97", "B: Option 98", "C: Option 99", "D: Option 100"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 26, "question": "According to the scenario, what is the variable cost per small suitcase after automation?", "options": ["A: Option 101", "B: Option 102", "C: Option 103", "D: Option 104"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 27, "question": "What is a mortgage?", "options": ["A: Option 105", "B: Option 106", "C: Option 107", "D: Option 108"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 28, "question": "According to the scenario, what was the average spend per customer in the last 11 months?", "options": ["A: Option 109", "B: Option 110", "C: Option 111", "D: Option 112"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 29, "question": "Which one of the following pieces of legislation relating to safety is the Bricknell bookshop likely to be in breach of?", "options": ["A: Option 113", "B: Option 114", "C: Option 115", "D: Option 116"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 30, "question": "Which of the following is likely to be a positive social factor for Filmore Pancakes?", "options": ["A: Option 117", "B: Option 118", "C: Option 119", "D: Option 120"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 31, "question": "Which of the following is an example of being enterprising?", "options": ["A: Option 121", "B: Option 122", "C: Option 123", "D: Option 124"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 32, "question": "A business with a USP has an advantage over its competitors. What is meant by the term "USP"?", "options": ["A: Option 125", "B: Option 126", "C: Option 127", "D: Option 128"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 33, "question": "Which of the following is an example of empowerment?", "options": ["A: Option 129", "B: Option 130", "C: Option 131", "D: Option 132"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 34, "question": "A fine is given to a business that:", "options": ["A: Option 133", "B: Option 134", "C: Option 135", "D: Option 136"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 35, "question": "A Memorandum of Association is an administrative requirement of a:", "options": ["A: Option 137", "B: Option 138", "C: Option 139", "D: Option 140"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 36, "question": "Ignoring the concerns of employees is most likely to lead to:", "options": ["A: Option 141", "B: Option 142", "C: Option 143", "D: Option 144"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 37, "question": "The wine producer"s profit for last year was:", "options": ["A: Option 145", "B: Option 146", "C: Option 147", "D: Option 148"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 38, "question": "A lack of communication between business functions:", "options": ["A: Option 149", "B: Option 150", "C: Option 151", "D: Option 152"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 39, "question": "Which of the following would be classified as variable costs of a hair salon?", "options": ["A: Option 153", "B: Option 154", "C: Option 155", "D: Option 156"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 40, "question": "Which of the following is/are not found on an organisation chart?", "options": ["A: Option 157", "B: Option 158", "C: Option 159", "D: Option 160"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 41, "question": "Which of the following would "a change of government policy" be an example of?", "options": ["A: Option 161", "B: Option 162", "C: Option 163", "D: Option 164"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 42, "question": "A car manufacturer is currently producing 320 000 cars per year with a margin of safety of 210 000 cars. The car manufacturer"s break-even point is:", "options": ["A: Option 165", "B: Option 166", "C: Option 167", "D: Option 168"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 43, "question": "Which one of the following would increase business uncertainty?", "options": ["A: Option 169", "B: Option 170", "C: Option 171", "D: Option 172"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 44, "question": "An income statement is used to:", "options": ["A: Option 173", "B: Option 174", "C: Option 175", "D: Option 176"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 45, "question": "Which of the following businesses is most likely to be negatively affected by an increase in interest rates?", "options": ["A: Option 177", "B: Option 178", "C: Option 179", "D: Option 180"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 46, "question": "Which of the following would be classified as non-current assets in the statement of financial position of a furniture store?", "options": ["A: Option 181", "B: Option 182", "C: Option 183", "D: Option 184"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 47, "question": "A potential investor is likely to want a business to:", "options": ["A: Option 185", "B: Option 186", "C: Option 187", "D: Option 188"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 48, "question": "In a SWOT analysis the letter "O" stands for:", "options": ["A: Option 189", "B: Option 190", "C: Option 191", "D: Option 192"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 49, "question": "Which of the following would this be an example of?", "options": ["A: Option 193", "B: Option 194", "C: Option 195", "D: Option 196"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 50, "question": "Which of the following is a requirement of the Partnership Act?", "options": ["A: Option 197", "B: Option 198", "C: Option 199", "D: Option 200"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 51, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a financial aim for a business?", "options": ["A: Option 201", "B: Option 202", "C: Option 203", "D: Option 204"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 52, "question": "A business with a unique selling point:", "options": ["A: Option 205", "B: Option 206", "C: Option 207", "D: Option 208"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 53, "question": "Which of the following is a non-legal consequence of failing to comply with the Data Protection Act?", "options": ["A: Option 209", "B: Option 210", "C: Option 211", "D: Option 212"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 54, "question": "Which one of the following job roles would report to a Director?", "options": ["A: Option 213", "B: Option 214", "C: Option 215", "D: Option 216"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 55, "question": "Paying the living wage is an example of:", "options": ["A: Option 217", "B: Option 218", "C: Option 219", "D: Option 220"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 56, "question": "Which of the following would not cause a business to fail?", "options": ["A: Option 221", "B: Option 222", "C: Option 223", "D: Option 224"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 57, "question": "A business that uses cross-functional teams has:", "options": ["A: Option 225", "B: Option 226", "C: Option 227", "D: Option 228"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 58, "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of operating as a private limited company?", "options": ["A: Option 229", "B: Option 230", "C: Option 231", "D: Option 232"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 59, "question": "The sole trader"s revenue for the coming year is expected to be:", "options": ["A: Option 233", "B: Option 234", "C: Option 235", "D: Option 236"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 60, "question": "Which one of the following is not an example of being enterprising?", "options": ["A: Option 237", "B: Option 238", "C: Option 239", "D: Option 240"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 61, "question": "Job roles on the same level of an organisation chart have:", "options": ["A: Option 241", "B: Option 242", "C: Option 243", "D: Option 244"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 62, "question": "Which of the following would be a fixed cost for a car manufacturer?", "options": ["A: Option 245", "B: Option 246", "C: Option 247", "D: Option 248"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 63, "question": "Which of the following is most likely to be a government-owned organisation?", "options": ["A: Option 249", "B: Option 250", "C: Option 251", "D: Option 252"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 64, "question": "How is a business most likely to respond to a stakeholder with a high degree of influence?", "options": ["A: Option 253", "B: Option 254", "C: Option 255", "D: Option 256"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 65, "question": "Mulligan Butchers Ltd appears to have broken the:", "options": ["A: Option 257", "B: Option 258", "C: Option 259", "D: Option 260"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 66, "question": "If the selling price per bottle is £7.50, the break-even level of output would be:", "options": ["A: Option 261", "B: Option 262", "C: Option 263", "D: Option 264"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 67, "question": "Which one of the following actions should the restaurant take in response to this economic change?", "options": ["A: Option 265", "B: Option 266", "C: Option 267", "D: Option 268"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 68, "question": "In which category should "an increase in fuel taxation" be placed?", "options": ["A: Option 269", "B: Option 270", "C: Option 271", "D: Option 272"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 69, "question": "Which one of the following would be carried out by the accounting function in a large business?", "options": ["A: Option 273", "B: Option 274", "C: Option 275", "D: Option 276"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 70, "question": "In which section of a statement of financial position would "inventory" appear?", "options": ["A: Option 277", "B: Option 278", "C: Option 279", "D: Option 280"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 71, "question": "Which of the following is an example of a financial aim for a business?", "options": ["A: Option 281", "B: Option 282", "C: Option 283", "D: Option 284"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 72, "question": "A business with a unique selling point:", "options": ["A: Option 285", "B: Option 286", "C: Option 287", "D: Option 288"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 73, "question": "Which of the following is a non-legal consequence of failing to comply with the Data Protection Act?", "options": ["A: Option 289", "B: Option 290", "C: Option 291", "D: Option 292"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 74, "question": "Which one of the following job roles would report to a Director?", "options": ["A: Option 293", "B: Option 294", "C: Option 295", "D: Option 296"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 75, "question": "Paying the living wage is an example of:", "options": ["A: Option 297", "B: Option 298", "C: Option 299", "D: Option 300"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 76, "question": "Which of the following would not cause a business to fail?", "options": ["A: Option 301", "B: Option 302", "C: Option 303", "D: Option 304"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 77, "question": "A business that uses cross-functional teams has:", "options": ["A: Option 305", "B: Option 306", "C: Option 307", "D: Option 308"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 78, "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of operating as a private limited company?", "options": ["A: Option 309", "B: Option 310", "C: Option 311", "D: Option 312"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 79, "question": "The sole trader"s revenue for the coming year is expected to be:", "options": ["A: Option 313", "B: Option 314", "C: Option 315", "D: Option 316"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}, {"id": 80, "question": "Which one of the following is not an example of being enterprising?", "options": ["A: Option 317", "B: Option 318", "C: Option 319", "D: Option 320"], "correctAnswer": "A", "marks": 1}];